Hey, Emma, you better appreciate this while it lasts..
嘿, 艾玛 你最好现在感谢这个还能支撑你..
because when you get older, you're not gonna be able to just sit around all day.
因为当你长大了, 你就不能整天都坐着啦!
-So true. -Yeah.
-确实 -是啊
-Hey. -Hey.
-嘿！ -嘿！
We're here to say goodbye. We're off to Ohio.
我们来道别, 要去俄亥俄州
Oh, right, your adoption interview.
领养面试
Yep. We'll meet the lady who could be carrying our baby.
对方有可能是我们BB的妈妈
I can't believe it. When you come back, you'll have a baby. That is so weird.
难以置信, 你们回家时会带着BB!  很奇怪
And so incorrect.
也很不正确
She's only a couple months pregnant.
她怀孕没几个月
She liked our application but might not like us.
她选中了我们的申请表, 是否喜欢我们还不一定
Come on, she's gonna love you guys.
她会相中你们的!
Thank you. But we're trying not to get our hopes up.
谢谢, 我们满怀希望
A lot could still get in our way.
看运气吧
She could decide against adoption, like another couple better.
她可能会决定拒绝把孩子给人领养 也可能选中其他夫妇
What are you gonna name it?
你们打算给小孩取啥名字?
I could develop a condition in which I talk and talk and no one hears a word.
我就有这个本事，费尽口舌 而旁人却充耳不闻
But just think, okay? What if everything goes right?
试想, 如果一切顺利
What if this woman does pick you guys?
她真选了你们俩
Oh, my God. She's gonna pick us!
天!那她就会选我们
So we're standing firm on "not getting our hopes up"?
我们决心，决不轻易放弃希望
No. I know things could still go wrong, but if they don't..
我明白, 有可能出差错, 但万一顺利
if this works out, we're gonna have a baby. A baby!
我们就会有孩子了 一个孩子!
-Yes. But.. -Oh, my God. It's gonna work!
-是的，但是… -会成功的!
We're gonna make it work!
我们会尽力!
I'm gonna be a mommy, and you're gonna be a daddy!
我要当妈妈, 你要当爸爸
All right, I'll see you suckers. I'm gonna go get me a baby!
回见了笨蛋, 我要去领娃娃了
Screw it. I'm gonna be a daddy!
去你们的, 我要当爹啦
The One with the Birth Mother
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
Hey, who's Phoebe with?
菲比跟谁聊呢?
Mike.
麦克！
No, Joey. Who is Phoebe with at the door?
不，乔伊 和菲比站在门口的是谁?
I wanna say, "Someone I'm gonna have sex with."
我想说, 会跟我上床的姑娘
-Hey. -Hey.
-嘿！ -嘿！
-So who's your friend? -Oh, that's Sarah.
-你朋友? -莎拉
No. Don't you get any ideas.
不，你少打我朋友的主意！
I'm not setting you up with any more of my friends.
我再也不给你撮合我的朋友了
-Why? Why? -Because you'll date her once..
-为什么？为什么？ -你约会人家一次...
sleep with her, then forget she exists.
睡一个，然后就把人家忘到九霄云外
Name one friend of yours I did that with.
举例说明
-Mandy. -Mandy, huh?
-曼蒂 -曼蒂，是吗？
Really hot blond, big boobs?
金发丰胸辣妹?
-No. -Might be why I don't remember, huh?
-错 -我明白为什么会忘了她
Do you think I'm someone else?
你好象把我当别人了?
Look, I may not have treated your friends well in the past.
过去我也许待你朋友不公
But I have grown up a lot. Really. Honest. Rach?
但我现在成熟多了, 真的, 瑞秋
Yeah, believe it or not, it's true.
信不信由你, 是真的
I mean, when Joey and I were together..
乔伊和我交往的时候...
he was wonderful. He was thoughtful and mature.
很乖。体贴, 成熟
And for the one week that we went out..
我们交往那一周
he didn't sleep with anybody else.
他没和其他女人上床
Growth.
成长
-Fine, I'll give you her number. -Okay. Thank you.
-好, 给你她的电话号码 -谢谢。
And I promise you I will not forget this one.
我保证这个不忘记
-Mandy. -Sarah!
-曼蒂 -莎拉
Sarah.
莎拉
-Hey. -Hi.
-嘿！ -嗨！
-Hey. -Hey, guys, I need some fashion advice.
-嗨！ -嗨, 给点着装建议
How does this look?
帽子好看吗?
Well, it's.. It's a little low. Pick it up a little.
有点...抬高点, 再高, 再高, 好了
A little bit more.
再高
There you go.
好了
Now throw it away.
扔一边去
Come on! This looks good.
别这样, 是好帽子
Ross, please trust me. I buy 30 fashion magazines a month.
信我, 我一个月买30本时尚杂志
Now I don't know who's running for president or who that NATO guy is..
我不清楚谁在竞选总统, 也不知道NATO(北约)那家伙是谁
but I do know that you have to get far away from that hat.
但我知道, 你该离那帽子越远越妙
Damn it. God..
见鬼
I have this date tomorrow night, and I have to look cool.
明晚我要约会, 我得扮帅才行
-Well, who's the girl? -Her name's Joan.
-她是谁? -她叫琼
She's in fashion. She works for Hugo Boss.
她在时尚界工作 她在Hugo Boss（服装品牌）工作
Hugo Boss? I thought you said she was in fashion.
Hugo Boss?你不说她在时尚界工作?
At the Ralph Lauren offices, that would've killed.
在拉夫.劳伦的办公室说这些 你就死定了
If you want fashion help, Rachel and l are going shopping tomorrow.
如果你需要着装建议 明天我和瑞秋要去购物
-You're welcome to come with us. -Really? That would be great.
-欢迎同去 -真的?太好了
I mean, I have to do something.
我必须有备而去
She kind of teased me about how I dress.
她总是取笑我的衣着
I can see why. Nice shirt.
显然, 就凭你那衬衣
You're wearing the same shirt.
你和我穿得一样啊
Stupid Gap on every corner!
GAP公司的大路货!
Make yourselves comfortable, and I'll be back with Erica.
随便坐, 我带艾瑞卡过来
Okay, thank you.
好，谢啦！
Well, this is it.
总算到了, 你状态如何?
-Are you okay? -Yeah, it's just weird, you know?
-你状态如何? -很好, 对话会有点奇怪
It's like, "Hi, I'm Chandler. May I have the human growing inside you?"
"我叫钱德, 你体内的小人 可以给我养吗?"
You're gonna be great.
你会表现出色
你也是
Well, obviously.
那显然
Monica? Chandler? I'd like you to meet Erica.
莫妮卡, 钱德 这位是艾瑞卡
-Hi. -Hi. It is so, so nice to meet you.
-嗨！ -真高兴跟你见面
-Hi. -Thank you for agreeing to see us.
-嗨！ -谢谢你同意见我们
-Hi. -I'll let you get acquainted.
-嗨！ -你们熟悉一下
-Okay. -So it's Monica and Chandler?
-好的！ -莫妮卡和钱德?
I only know you as "File CRW33815-D."
你们的档案代号是“母牛3315-d号”
That's what our friends call us.
朋友们爱这么叫我们
Gosh, you know, you're just such an amazing couple. It's..
你们这一对令人羡慕
kind of intimidating.
简直叫人嫉妒
I don't know about that.
是吗?
Are you kidding me? I mean, it's enough that you're a doctor.
你在开玩笑吗?我是说， 您是医生
But on top of it, you're married to a reverend?
可您竟娶了个牧师!
-I don't think that's exactly.. -Let her finish, doctor.
-不是吧... -让她说完, 医生
-Hey. -Hey.
-嗨！ -嗨！
My friend Sarah had a great time last night.
莎拉昨晚跟你一起很愉快
-Yeah. -Yeah, so you gonna call this one back?
-是吗 -是啊, 这次你会再约她?
No.
绝不
What are you talking about? Sarah's great.
什么意思, 莎拉很棒
Oh, really? You want to know what your "great" friend did?
是吗?你知道你的很棒的朋友 干了什么好事?
We're out to dinner, okay?
我们出去吃饭
We were getting along, having a really nice time.
相处融洽, 和谐
I was thinking she was really cool.
我觉得她很可爱
And then, out of nowhere..
突然间
That's it?
就这样?
That's why you won't go out with her again?
这是你不理她的理由?
So she took some fries. Big deal.
吃你的薯条有什么大不了?
Hey, look, it's not about a few fries.
我不是气她吃我几根薯条
It's about what the fries represent.
你得清楚薯条的象征意义
-What? -All food!
-啥? -所有食物!!!
Well, I'm sorry.
对不起
I can't believe I set you up with such a monster!
竟然介绍你和"怪物"约会
Hey, look, I take a girl out..
我带女孩吃饭
she can order whatever she wants. The more the better, all right?
她点什么都可以, 多吃无妨
Just don't order a garden salad and then eat my food!
但不可以自己 只点沙拉却夺我的食物
That's a good way to lose some fingers.
这么做有可能被切手指的!
-Thank God you're here. Listen to this. -What?
-谢天谢地你来了, 你来评评理 -啥?
Joey and my friend are out last night, having dinner, and she reaches over..
乔伊昨晚约会我朋友.晚饭时...
-and takes a few of his fries.. -Oh, no!
-她伸手拿他的薯条 -天!
What?
这有什么?
You know about the plate thing?
你知道这条规则?
Oh, yeah, yeah. No, Joey doesn't share food.
我了解乔伊从不分享食物
I mean, just last week we were having breakfast..
上星期我们早餐时...
and he had a couple grapes on his plate.
他盘里有些葡萄
-You wouldn't let her have a grape? -No, not me.
-你不让她吃葡萄? -不是我
Emma.
是艾玛
Joey doesn't share food!
乔伊从不分享食物!!!
Well, I still think that is a stupid reason not to call someone again.
我坚持, 因为这条破事就 放弃好女孩很不明智
You are calling her, okay?
你再约她, 如果有必要
And if you need to, then just get an extra plate of fries for the table.
干脆再点一盘薯条不就完了?
I like that.
高
A sharing buffer. Yeah.
共享缓冲区
Yeah, I'll order some extra fries. Maybe a plate of onion rings.
多点一盘薯条 再点一盘洋葱
Yeah. Yeah.
好好！
And a shrimp cocktail.
还要冷盘虾
And some Buffalo wings.
和辣鸡翅
Maybe.. Maybe an individual pizza, huh?
或许，一份披萨
And some mozzarella sticks.
和牛排
What were we talking about?
我们在谈什么?
Wow, this place is awesome. Everyone is so mean.
哇, 这地方真吓人 人人都那么吝啬
So fun.
太有意思了!
We should just go. I'm not gonna find anything here.
我们走吧, 我在这淘不到什么的
This stuff is ridiculous.
这的东西都太可笑了
Oh, this place is great!
这地方真不赖!
Okay, you guys have fun. I'm gonna go talk to people in this voice.
好了, 你们开心吧 我要用这种声音和人聊天了
Rach, come on, I'm not gonna wear any of this. Nothing silver.
别, 我才不穿银色的
-Why? -Okay, nothing with hair.
-为什么？ -有毛毛领的
And nothing with padlocks on it!
更不穿带挂锁的
Ross, look. Look, I know that some of this stuff is out there.
我知道有些衣裳不入你眼
But I mean, come on, look at this. Look at this sweater.
但你看这件
I mean, this is just beautiful.
多美
Wow, this is really soft.
是很柔软
Three hundred and fifty dollars?
350元?
Down from 700. You're saving, like,200 bucks.
从700块打折下来!你差不多省了200块!
Both logic and math are taking a serious hit today.
逻辑学和数学都饱受摧残
Hey, check this out. It's totally you.
这件好, 很衬你
-Wow. -Yeah.
-哇哦！ -嗯
Wow. Actually, this looks pretty good.
哇哦！这件看起来不错。
Yeah.
是啊！
"Boys will be boys"?
"孩子就是孩子"(舞曲名)?
-What? They will be! -All right.
-本来就是! -好好。
-That's it, I'm getting out of here. -No, Ross, wait, come on.
-算了, 我走 -别，罗斯，等等嘛！
There's other stuff here. There's some nice shirts, these nice pants.
还有其他的呢， 衣裳和裤子都不错
Actually, these might look pretty good on me.
其实，这些看起来挺适合我
Yes, they will. You know what you should do? Go take a walk.
嗯，不错。这样, 你随便转转先
All right? I know your size, and I'll pick out some really good stuff for you.
我知道你尺码, 我帮你挑些真正的好东西
-Really? -Yes.
-当真? -对
I know what looks sexy on guys.
我知道男人穿什么最性感
Just wear what I suggest, and she is gonna go nuts for you.
穿我推荐的衣服, 不迷死她才怪
So you're saying..
你是说…
if I wear these pants, I might be getting into hers?
我若穿这条裤子，她会允许我侵犯?
Why do men keep talking to me like this?
为什么男人老跟我来这套?
So the fact that I'm a doctor and my wife's a reverend..
我是医生, 我太太是牧师,
that's important to you?
这对你很重要?
Yeah. I read some great applications..
是啊, 很多申请人都很优秀
but I thought, "Who better than a minister to raise a child?"
但是, 带孩子谁也比不上牧师
Amen.
阿门
Plus, I thought the baby would be in good hands with a doctor.
何况还有医生的妙手
Good hands.
很好的一双手。
Healing hands.
疗伤圣手
Reverend, can I ask? Does the Bible say anything about adoption?
牧师, 圣经上有写领养孩子吗?
It says, "Do it."
写了:但做无妨!
"And behold, she did adopt unto them a baby.
(模仿圣经句式:)她让他们领养了一个婴孩 (原为"你要怀孕生子，可以给他起名叫耶稣")
And it was good."
(继续:)此乃善举
-Wow. -Yeah, wow.
-哇 -我也哇
I was wondering.. You both have such serious jobs.
我在想 你们工作都责任重大
Would you have time to take care of a baby and your flock?
有时间照顾BB? 还兼顾你的教友们?
-My flock? -People in your church.
-我的教友？ -你们教堂里的人。
Oh, my flock.
哦，我的教友。
Oh, no, my flock? My flock is good.
我的教友? 我的教友们很不错
Yeah. My flock pretty much takes care of themselves by this point.
现在他们能照顾自己
Good flock. Flock, flock, flock.
好教友，好教友
But being a doctor, that must take up a lot of time.
当医生很花时间吧?
Not for me it doesn't.
我的情况不同
So how's everything going in here?
谈得如何?
We're great. I think I may have asked all my questions.
问题问完了，很满意
Good. Do you have questions for Erica?
你们有什么要问她?
Yeah, actually. So you read a file that you liked..
我想问问, 你读到满意的申请表
and then you gave the agency the serial number and they contacted us?
然后告诉代理人编号 然后他们联系到我们?
Yes. Our system ensures total anonymity.
我们的系统中用户完全匿名
-We're very proud of it. -You should be.
-我们以此为荣 -应该骄傲
You're really on top of stuff.
一流
Well then, if there's nothing else, then the two of us should talk.
别的没什么了?那我们俩谈谈
I actually..
实际上…
-I don't think we have to. -We don't?
-我想我们不必谈了 -为什么不？
Yeah, when I read about you two, I was pretty sure I wanted you..
我看了你们的 档案就确定要选你们
but I just thought we should meet face to face.
但还想当面见见你们
I've made my decision.
我决定了, 就选他们
I choose them.
就选他们
Oh, my God, this is great.
哦，天啊，太棒了
This is so great. Did you hear that?
太棒了，听见吗
Yeah, I did.
是的，听见了
Hey.
嘿！
Thank you. Thank you so much.
谢谢，太谢谢了
You are so going to heaven!
你将来一定进天堂!
-We got some really great stuff. -Yeah.
-我们买了些很棒的东西。 -对！
Yeah, but I'm not sure about some of the bras I got.
但是，有些胸罩似乎不妥
Really? Do you want to try some of them on for me?
真的?你能穿上试给我看吗？
Okay.
好
Wait, are we in Joey's imagination?
等一下，我们是在乔伊的幻想里?
Oh, no. I took one of Ross' bags by mistake.
糟糕, 错拿罗斯一袋
And one of mine is missing.
我那件不见了
Ross probably has it. You'll get it from him later.
肯定在罗斯那里, 找他拿回来好了
So, what do you think?
如何?
I think we're not wearing the same shirt anymore.
这次我们可没穿一样!
Yeah. Yeah, Rachel picked it out for me.
对，瑞秋帮我选的
She told me to trust her, and you know what? I'm glad I did.
她让我相信她 真高兴我答应了, 一路回头率暴高!
I turned quite a few heads on my way over here.
在来的路上, 有很多人看我
Dude, I really don't think you should be wearing that.
老兄, 别穿成这样
I see.
我明白
Somebody's afraid of a little competition with the ladies?
有人怕我抢走了女人的目光
Looks like someone is the ladies!
有人好象变了女人!
You're just jealous because you couldn't pull this off.
你嫉妒, 因为你没出风头
Yeah. Now if you'll excuse me, I have a date.
现在失陪了, 我约会去
See? All eyes on me!
看到没？大家都只看我!
-We are not signing those papers. -Why not?
-不能签 -为啥?
It's wrong. They made a mistake. They think we're somebody else.
这不对, 他们搞错, 当我们是别人
God works in mysterious ways.
上帝的安排, 凡人懂什么
You have got to stop.
别再冒充!
But she liked us.
但她喜欢我们
She likes Doctor Chandler and Reverend Monica.
她喜欢的是钱德医生和莫妮卡牧师
If you think about it, I'm kind of like a reverend.
回想一下，我其实满像牧师
I mean, as a chef, I serve God by feeding the hungry and poor.
作为厨子, 我给饥饿的人和穷人提供食物 这不也是为上帝服务?
Your veal chop is 34.95!
你一份牛排卖34块9毛5!
Come on, I just.. I think we've been given an opportunity.
得了, 机会敲门
The mistake's already made. They're writing up the papers now.
不如将错就错, 他们都在签协议了
But we're not the ones she chose.
但我们是冒充的
How can you feel okay about this?
你竟然理直气壮
Because.
因为…
We may not be who she thinks we are..
虽然我们不是她选中的人
but no one will ever love that baby more than us.
但没人比我们更爱那个小娃娃
-I know. -I mean, who knows..
-我明白 -我的意思是
how long it's gonna take for someone else to give us a baby?
谁知道我们到底还要等多久 才会有人给我们BB?
What if no one ever picks us?
万一永远没人选我们?
Oh, honey..
哦，亲爱的
Please?
行吗？
Please. We are so close.
求你了，我们就快成功了
Monica, I want a baby too.
莫妮卡，我也想要孩子
But this woman is giving away her child.
但她要送出她的心肝宝贝
She deserves to know who it's going to.
她应该知道对方的真实身份
Okay. You're right.
好吧，你说的没错
So we'll tell the truth.
我们跟她摊牌,
And who knows, you know? Maybe she'll like us for us.
而且谁知道呢, 对吧? 没准，她喜欢的是咱俩本人
Maybe she will.
或许！
Why couldn't I have been a reverend?
我怎么就不是牧师呢!
You're Jewish.
你是犹太教的
Technicality!
差别不大!
Garden salad for the lady.
女士点的戈登沙拉
Oh, that looks great. Good ordering.
看来很诱人, 真会点
Seafood platter for the gentleman, and extra fries.
男士点的海鲜拼盘, 另有一盘薯条, 请慢用
Enjoy.
请慢用
Those fries look delicious.
薯条很美味
I didn't know you liked French fries.
你也喜欢吃法国薯条?
Help yourself. What's mine is yours.
吃吧, 我的就是你的
Wow, are those stuffed clams?
好大的清蒸粉蚌
Yes, they are my stuffed clams.
对, 是我的清蒸粉蚌
How about those fries, though, huh?
吃薯条如何?
-They are delicious. -Yeah.
-真美味 -是啊
You are beautiful, you know that?
你真漂亮，知道吗
That is so sweet.
你好甜
Okay, then.
喂！
Now look what you did!
你捣什么乱!
What? What is the matter with you?
怎么回事?
I don't like it when people take food off of my plate, okay?
我不喜欢别人抢我的东西吃
But you said, "What's mine is yours."
但你说过"我的就是你的"
Well, I didn't mean it!
我言不由衷!
Fine. Sorry, I didn't think it was that big a deal.
好吧, 对不起, 没想到你这么在乎
No, I'm sorry. I..
抱歉
I'm overreacting, okay? It's just, when it comes to food, I..
反应过激, 食物方面
have certain rules..
我有一些戒律
okay? I mean..
我是说
there are things you do, and, you know, things that you don't do.
有些事可以做, 有些事就不可以
Wow, this place looks great.
这儿很不错
Oh, you are gonna love it. And I'm so glad we're finally doing this.
你会喜欢的, 真高兴我们在一起
-Me too. -Here.
-我也是 -这儿
So this was fun.
真有趣！
I really am sorry about, you know, before.
刚才的事真抱歉
And I want to make sure you know I really do like you.
我想说, 我真的喜欢你
Sure, just not as much as clams.
是啊, 但是没有喜欢蛤蚌那么多
Well, stuffed clams..
清蒸粉蚌
Chocolate torte for the lady.
女士要的巧克力甜品
Cheesecake for the gentleman.
男士的奶酪蛋糕
Excuse me, sir. There seems to be some sort of red crap on my cheesecake.
抱歉，我的蛋糕上不是应该有些红葡萄吗？
Yes, that's a raspberry coulis.
是的，那是覆盆子
Coulis is not a monkey?
覆盆子不是一种猴子吗?
When I read the description I thought it came with a little raspberry monkey.
当我看到覆盆子这个词的时候 我还以为是一种猴子呢！
-Oh, my God. -I'll just have what she's having instead.
-哦，天啊 -我要换成她那种
Oh, I'm sorry, sir. That was our last piece.
抱歉先生，那是最后一块了
I'm so stupid ordering cheesecake, trying to be healthy.
点奶酪蛋糕真够蠢, 还说健康食品呢
Oh, no.
哦，不
This is work. I should call in. Can you excuse me?
天啊, 真好吃 工作电话, 我得复机
Yeah, sure. No problem.
请便
What are you doing? I thought you don't share food?
干嘛?你不是不和人分享食物?
Sure I do.
才没有, 吃点我的
Coulis?
覆盆子？
No. If I can't have your clams, you can't have my dessert.
不，我都不能吃你的蛤蚌 你也不能碰我的甜品
This is a two-way street.
规则是双向的
Really?
是吗?
Really.
是的。
Now this all better be here when I come back.
我回来时希望它完好无损
Yeah, of course. I can control myself.
当然, 我能控制自己
Stop staring at me!
别再瞪着我!
Just a tiny little..
就一小口
I'm not even sorry.
我甚至不抱歉
-Hi. -Hey.
-嗨！ -嗨！
So these are the preliminary forms for an open adoption.
领养的初步手续就这些了
There's a lot to go over, but I'll explain as we go through.
后续的手续还很多, 希望一切顺利
-Is that a picture? -Yeah.
-孩子的照片? -对
It's a sonogram they took of the baby last week.
是上周给bb拍的B超
I thought you might want to see it.
你们也许有兴趣看看
Look, doctor.
医生快看
Look, before we sign anything, we really have to talk.
签字前我们得谈谈
We're not who you think we are.
我们不是你选中的夫妇
-I don't understand. -The agency must have made a mistake.
-什么意思? -代理公司肯定出错了
My wife is not a reverend, and I'm not a doctor.
我太太不是牧师, 我不是医生
-What? -That's impossible.
-啊? -不可能
I could perform an operation on you and prove it if you'd like.
我可以替你开刀, 向你证明
I have to check your file. Excuse me.
我去查档案，抱歉失陪
So who are you?
你们到底是谁?
Our names really are Monica and Chandler. We're from New York.
我们是叫莫妮卡, 钱德, 纽约来的
Yeah, but the important thing to know about us..
但重要的是
is how much we would care for this little baby.
我们真的很爱这个小孩
So you lied to me before?
你们先前跟我撒谎?
Well, we "bore false witness."
我们起“假誓”
See? I could be a reverend.
看, 我真有当牧师的天赋
I can't believe this.
我真不敢相信
But we were hoping that since we told you the truth..
我们希望说明真相后
-that you still might consider.. -Giving you my baby?
-你能网开一面 -把我的宝贝给你们?
You think I'd give you my child after this?
把孩子给两个骗子?
You don't have to decide now. If you look at our file..
不必马上决定，请看看我们的档案
I don't want to look at your file. This is over.
没兴趣, 到此为止
Erica, wait.
Erica 请等等,
I have nothing to say to you.
我跟你无话可说
Look, you have every reason to be upset.
你很有理由生气
We did lie.
我们是撒了谎
But only because we've been waiting and trying to have a baby for so long.
但那是因为我们想要个孩子等太久了
And we don't know how long it's gonna be before we get another chance.
我们也不知道下一个机会 何年何月才会到来
Why don't you ask the reverend to pray on it?
让你的牧师祈祷去吧!
Erica, please.
Erica, 等等
Just consider us. Ask them to see our file.
考虑一下我们吧 找他们要我们的资料
Our last name's Bing.
我们姓宾
My wife's a chef, and I'm in advertising.
我太太是大厨，我从事广告业
Oh, yeah.
嗯
I actually liked you guys.
我的确喜欢你们
But it doesn't matter. What you did was wrong.
但你们不该撒谎
But you did like us.
但你喜欢我们对不对
And you should.
你没有喜欢错
My wife's an incredible woman.
我太太很了不起
She is loving, and devoted and caring.
有爱心, 乐于奉献, 关怀他人
And don't tell her I said this, but the woman's always right.
别告诉她我这么说 而且她一贯正确
I love my wife more than anything in this world.
我爱我太太胜过世上一切事物
And it..
所以..
It kills me that I can't give her a baby.
不能给她个孩子, 我难受得要命
I really want a kid.
我很想要孩子
And when that day finally comes, I'll learn how to be a good dad.
有了孩子以后 我会学习如何做是个好爸爸
But my wife..
但我太太…
she's already there.
她已经是个好妈妈
She's a mother..
她是一个妈妈
without a baby.
可惜没孩子
Please?
求你了
You still want that baby?
你还要那孩子吗?
God bless you, Chandler Bing!
上帝保佑你，钱德宾
Turns out this sweater is made for a woman.
原来这是女人穿的
So why are you still wearing it?
那你还穿?
Because it's soft.
柔软。
Hey, so how was your date?
今天过得如何?
Not so good.
不太好
Well, looks like it's just the two of us tonight, huh, buddy?
就咱俩是倒霉蛋
Yeah. And you know what? We could do a lot worse.
是啊, 还有更倒霉的时候呢
-Yeah. -Yeah.
-是阿 -嗯
Joey doesn't share food!
乔伊从不分享食物!